This time, you are supposed to find A+B where A and B are two polynomials.

Input

Each input file contains one test case. Each case occupies 2 lines, and each line contains the information of a polynomial: K N1 aN1 N2 aN2 ... NK aNK, where K is the number of nonzero terms in the polynomial, Ni and aNi (i=1, 2, ..., K) are the exponents and coefficients, respectively. It is given that 1 <= K <= 10，0 <= NK < ... < N2 < N1 <=1000.

Output

For each test case you should output the sum of A and B in one line, with the same format as the input. Notice that there must be NO extra space at the end of each line. Please be accurate to 1 decimal place.

Sample Input

2 1 2.4 0 3.2

2 2 1.5 1 0.5

Sample Output

3 2 1.5 1 2.9 0 3.2